{
    "subject": "resource/Namma_Metro",
    "predicate": "property/owner",
    "object": "Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation Ltd.",
    "human_readable": "Namma Metro's owner is Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation Ltd.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866799712181091,
            "question": "Is Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation Ltd. responsible for Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9795301556587219,
            "question": "If Namma Metro is owned by Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation Ltd., who might be responsible for its operation and maintenance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8909175395965576,
            "question": "Can you name a public transportation system owned by Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation Ltd.?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8888569474220276,
            "question": "Who owns Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8217728734016418,
            "question": "What could 'Ltd.' stand for in the name of the organization that owns Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8203928470611572,
            "question": "What is the full name of the organization that owns Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8025767207145691,
            "question": "What type of organization owns Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.723612904548645,
            "question": "Which city's metro system is Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6606910228729248,
            "question": "Why do you think it's important to know who owns Namma Metro?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3568776845932007,
            "question": "What does the acronym 'Namma Metro' likely stand for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Namma Metro's owner is Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation Ltd.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6371_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why do you think it's important to know who owns Namma Metro?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6371_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which city's metro system is Namma Metro?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6371_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of organization owns Namma Metro?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6371_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6371_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that the Bangalore Metro, known as Namma Metro, is owned and operated by the Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation Limited (BMRCL). Therefore, the statement \"Namma Metro's owner is Bangalore Metro Rail Corporation Ltd\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}